RG 079:001, Department of Environmental Protection: Central Office
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Commissioner, 1957-2004
  - Stanley J. Pac, 1973-1987
    - Subject Files, 1977-1980; 1988-030
      - Governor’s Office, 1980 February (Box 28-3)
      - Governor’s Office, 1980 March (Box 28-3)
      - Governor’s Office, 1980 April (Box 28-3)
      - Governor’s Office, 1980 May (Box 28-3)
      - Governor’s Office, 1980 June (Box 28-3)
  - Leslie A. Carothers, 1987-1990
    - Chronological Files, 1987-1990; 1993-139
      - 1990 February-January (Box 1)
      - 1990 March-April (Box 1)
      - 1990 May-July (Box 1)
      - 1990 August-September (Box 1)
      - 1990 October-November (Box 1)
      - 1990 December-1991 January (Box 1)
      - Governor's responses, 1988 June 6 - 1988 October 21 (Box 1)
      - Governor's responses, 1988 July 6 - August (Box 1)
      - Lake Williams (Box 1)
      - Farmington Canal Rail Corridor (Box 1)
      - Tom's chronological file (Box 1)
      - 1988 January-June (Box 1)
      - Draft response for Governor's signature, 1989 November - 1990 June 1 (Box 1)
      - Draft response for Governor's signature, 1989 March - April (Box 1)
      - Governor's draft responses, 1989 November (Box 1)
      - Governor's reponses to 1989 February (Box 1)
      - Governor's responses, 1989 April - July (Box 2)
      - Carother's letters, 1989 July - December (Box 2)
      - 1989 July-October (Box 2)
      - Consolidated files, 1989 April - June (Box 2)
      - 1989 January 11 - March 31 (Box 2)
      - 1988 December - 1989 March 20 (Box 2)
      - 1988 October 3 - December 28 (Box 2)
      - 1988 June 1 - September 29 (Box 2)
      - 1987 February 25 - 1987 July 24 (Box 2)
      - 1988 March 9 - May 31 (Box 2)
      - Letters, 1987 November - Decenber (Box 2)
      - Chronological file, 1987 January - December (Box 2)
      - Letters, 1987 March, July, September, October (Box 2)
    - Speeches, 1987-1990; 1994-010 (part) (Box 2)
  - Timothy R. E. Keeney, 1991-1994
    - Subject Files, 1991-1995; 1996-009
      - Avery Point (Box 1)
      - Boating certification (Box 1)
      - Boating fatality (Box 1)
      - Beardsley Park (Box 1)
      - DEP magazine (Box 1)
      - Disasters/Natural (Box 1)
      - E-2000 Conference (Box 1)
      - Earth Week 1995 (Box 1)
      - Entrepreneurial Center RFP (Box 1)
      - Environmental Industries / CT Environmental Entrepreneurial Center (Box 1)
      - Environmental Justice / Equity (Box 1)
      - EPA (Box 1)
      - Fairfield Hill Hospital (Box 1)
      - Frankel (Box 1)
      - Geoclean Environmental (Box 1)
      - Galaxy Mall (Box 1)
      - Greenways (Box 1)
      - Green Industries (Box 1)
      - Recreation and Natural Heritage Trust Program (Box 1)
      - Land conservation (Box 1)
      - Lead abatement (Box 1)
      - Low Emission Vehicle (LEV) (Box 1)
      - Lattin's Cove (Box 1)
      - Long Island Sound Plate (Box 1)
      - Long Island Sound Advisory Committee (Box 1)
      - Long Island Sound Programs (Box 1)
      - Lisbon (Box 1)
      - Low level radioactive waste (Box 1)
      - Lyman Orchards (Box 1)
      - Mashantucket Pequot (Box 1)
      - Mohegan Reservation (Box 1)
      - Mosquito control / Marsh restoration (Box 1)
      - Mute swans (Box 1)
      - Naval sub base / Dredging (Box 1)
      - Parks (Box 1)
      - Pollution prevention (Box 1)
      - Polymer (Box 1)
      - Raymark (Box 1)
      - Rising Pond Dam (Box 1)
      - Rivers Management (Box 1)
      - Silver Lake (Box 1)
      - Session Woods (Box 1)
      - Solectria (Box 1)
      - Somers / Rye Hill Circle (Box 1)
      - Sportsmen / Hunting issues (Box 1)
      - Stadium project (Box 1)
      - Susan Starr / Decision (Box 1)
      - State Guard (Box 1)
      - Trashmore (Box 1)
      - UConn - Marine acquaculture (Box 1)
      - Unredeemed bottle deposits (Box 1)
      - Wesleyan Camp (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1994; 1995-038
      - Representatives and Governor’s log letters (Responses), 1994 (Box 1)
      - FOIA Requests, 1994 (Box 1)
      - Representatives and Governor’s log letters (Responses), 1993 (Box 1)
      - Representatives and Governor’s log letters (Responses), 1993 (Box 2)
      - Representatives and Governor’s log letters (Responses), 1992 (Box 2)
      - Representatives and Governor’s log letters (Responses), 1992 (Box 3)
      - Representatives and Governor’s log letters (Responses), 1991 (Box 3)
      - Deputy Commissioner’s letters (Responses), 1991-1994 (Box 3)
      - Commissioner’s letters (Responses), 1991-1994 (Box 3)
    - Speeches, 1992-1993; 1995-039 (Box 1)
    - Speeches, 1991; 1994-010 (part) (Box 1)
  - Sidney J. Holbrook, 1995-1997
    - 2001-040
      - Correspondence
        - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1)
          Arranged alphabetically.
        - Governor's log letters, 1996 (Box 1)
          Arranged numerically.
        - Log letters, 1996 (Box 3)
      - Subject Files, 1995-1996
        - Air (Box 2)
        - Amtrack (Box 2)
        - Evans, Bill (Box 2)
        - Firearms inventory (Box 2)
        - Governor issues, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
        - Governor, 1995 (Box 2)
        - Governor, 1996 (Box 2)
        - Governor - Memos - Trips, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
        - Holbrook, Sid (Box 2)
        - Holbrook, Sid - Car (Box 2)
        - Holbrook, Sid - Phones (Box 2)
        - Leff, David (Box 2)
        - Legal (Box 2)
        - Legislators (Box 2)
        - Long Island Sound (Box 2)
        - Memos, 1995 (Box 2)
        - Memos, 1996 (Box 2)
        - Natural resources (Box 2)
        - Outdoor recreation (Box 2)
        - One / Chane, Inc. (Box 2)
        - Personnel, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
        - S (Box 2)
        - U (Box 2)
        - Waste (Box 2)
        - Water (Box 2)
        - Work hours (Box 2)
      - Subject Files, 1997
        - Attorney General, 1997 (Box 4)
        - Attorney General, 1996 (Box 4)
        - Attorney General, 1995 (Box 4)
        - Air Management (Box 4)
        - Air Bureau - Contract (Box 4)
        - Appointments (Box 4)
        - B (Box 4)
        - Beardsley Zoo (Box 4)
        - Barlow, D. / Bond agenda requests (Box 4)
        - Beehive Stadium (Box 4)
        - Bonding (Box 4)
        - Birthdays (Box 4)
        - Bridgeport (Box 4)
        - Budget (Box 4)
        - C (Box 4)
        - CBIA (Box 4)
        - Commissioners (Box 4)
        - Danbury (Box 4)
        - Delegation of authority (Box 4)
        - Emissions - New Jersey/Connecticut (Box 4)
        - Enforcement action / violations - pending (Box 4)
        - EPA (Box 4)
        - Evans, Bill (Box 4)
        - FERC (Box 4)
        - Flounder, Summer (Box 4)
        - G (Box 4)
        - General funds (Box 4)
        - Governor's Office, 1997 (Box 4)
        - Handy & Harman (Box 4)
        - Holbrook, Sid (Box 4)
        - Holbrook, Sid - Car (Box 4)
        - Holbrook, Sid - Phones (Box 4)
        - Johnson, Doris (Box 4)
        - K (Box 4)
        - Kellogg (Box 4)
        - Lajoie, Sue (Box 4)
        - Leff, David (Box 4)
        - Legal (Box 4)
        - Legislators (Box 4)
        - Licensed environmental professional(LEP) regulations (Box 4)
        - Licensed environmental professional(LEP), 2 folders (Box 4)
        - M (Box 4)
        - Memos (Box 4)
        - Mohegan destination report (Box 4)
        - Mosquito program (Box 4)
        - Natural resources (Box 4)
        - New London file (Box 4)
        - Northeast Utilities (Box 4)
        - O (Box 4)
        - OPM (Box 4)
        - Old Saybrook (Box 4)
        - Outdoor recreation (Box 4)
        - P (Box 4)
        - PEER (Box 4)
        - Permits (Box 4)
        - Personnel (Box 4)
        - Photos (Box 4)
        - Pleasure Beach Bridge (Box 4)
        - Policy self policing (Box 4)
        - Political activity (Box 4)
        - Pollution prevention (Box 4)
        - Pratt & Whitney (Box 4)
        - Precision timer (Box 4)
        - Putnam Memorial State Park (Box 4)
        - R (Box 4)
        - Regs (Box 4)
        - Rocque, Art - LIS (Box 4)
        - Route 6 (Box 4)
        - S (Box 4)
        - Safe Way (Box 4)
        - Santarsiero, Vito (Box 4)
        - Security (Box 4)
        - Shakespeare Theater (Box 4)
        - Staff meeting (Box 5)
        - Sullivan, M. (Box 5)
        - Survey response (Box 5)
        - T (Box 5)
        - Telephone coverage (Box 5)
        - Volunteers - Thank you (Box 5)
        - W (Box 5)
        - Waste management (Box 5)
        - Water management (Box 5)
        - Waterbury Rolling Mills (Box 5)
        - Web trends (Box 5)
        - Whale (Box 5)
        - Y (Box 5)
        - Yaworski (Box 5)
        - Correspondence log records, 1995-1997; 4 folders (Box 5)
        - OSHA citation at DEP, 1988-1995; 1 binder (Box 5)
        - Plasticrete-Quinnipiac River Incident Case # 95-5697, 1995; 1 binder (Box 5)
    - 1998-036 (part)
      - Speeches, 1995-1997; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Arthur J. Rocque, Jr., 1998-2004
    - 2003-033 (part)
      - Log letters, 1998-2001
        - 1998 (Box 11)
        - 1999 (Box 12)
        - 2000 (Box 13)
        - 2001 (Box 14)
      - Inside Out newsletters, 1995-1997; 58 issues (Box Unnumbered box)
    - 2005-009
      - Correspondence, 1998-2004
        - Governor's Office (Box 1)
          - Chief of Staff Peter Ellef (Box 1)
          - Chief of Staff Sidney J. Holbrook (Box 1)
          - Greater Bridgeport Interfaith Action (Box 1)
          - Guide of Ethics for Public Officials (Box 1)
        - Commissioner's Office (Box 1)
          - Budget Information (Box 1)
          - Legislative Program review Committee Confidentiality Agreement (Box 1)
          - Testimony from confirmation hearing (Box 1)
          - Commissioner Rocque's testimony before Executive and Legislative Nominations Committee (Box 1)
          - Commissioner Rocque's confirmation hearing materials (Box 1)
          - Confirmation correspondence (Box 1)
          - Strategic business plan (Box 1)
          - Auditor's correspondence, 1999 (Box 1)
          - Enforcement Program, Policy and Practices Group (Box 1)
          - Center for Strategic & International Studies, 1998 (Box 1)
          - Brass Mill Mall, 1998 (Box 1)
          - DEP reorganization, 1998 (Box 1)
          - AIR Bureau reorganization (Box 1)
          - Waste Bureau reorganization (Box 1)
          - Regional Water Authority - Re: The Watershed Fund (Box 1)
          - Bradley International Airport consent order (Box 1)
          - Brookfield condominium (Box 1)
          - Brookfield condominium engineering evaluation (Box 1)
          - Clean Water Fund analysis (Box 1)
          - Millennium Project (Box 1)
          - MOU DEP and DOH (Box 1)
          - United Aluminum Corporation penalty (Box 1)
          - University of Connecticut landfill consent order (Box 1)
        - Office of Legal Counsel (Box 1)
        - Assistant Commissioner David Leff (Box 1)
          - Open space (Box 1)
          - James V. Spignesi, Jr. (Box 1)
        - Governor's Office (Box 2)
        - Attorney General Richard Blumenthal (Box 2)
        - State Ethics Commission (Box 2)
        - Commissioner's correspondence (Box 2)
          - One stop / IT Project (Box 2)
          - DEP P4 Labor / Management Committee (Box 2)
          - Office of Policy and Management - Secretary Marc Ryan (Box 2)
          - DEP budget reduction options to the Office of Policy and Management (Box 2)
          - Reorganization issues (Box 2)
          - Delegation of authority (Box 2)
          - Correspondence, 2000 September-December (Box 2)
        - Ethics Commission, 1995 (Box 3)
        - Auditor's report, 1996 (Box 3)
        - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 3)
        - Candidates for Affirmative Action Administrator position, 1997 (Box 3)
        - Governor's correspondence / Commissioner's appointment, 1997 (Box 3)
        - Commissioner's correspondence, 1997 (Box 3)
        - Executive and Legislative Nomination Committee - Commissioner's testimony (Box 3)
        - Delegation of Authority, 1997 (Box 3)
        - Commissioner Sidney Holbrook, 1997 (Box 3)
        - Commissioner Arthur J. Rocque's correspondence, 1998 (Box 3)
        - Commissioner Arthur J. Rocque's correspondence, 1999 (Box 3)
        - Commissioner Arthur J. Rocque's correspondence, 2000 (Box 3)
        - Commissioner Arthur J. Rocque's correspondence, 2001 November-December (Box 4)
        - Commissioner Arthur J. Rocque's correspondence, 2001 September-October (Box 4)
        - Commissioner Arthur J. Rocque's correspondence, 2001 January-March (Box 4)
        - Commissioner Arthur J. Rocque's correspondence, 2001 April-June (Box 4)
        - Commissioner Arthur J. Rocque's correspondence, 2002 January-December (Box 4)
        - English Station (Box 4)
        - Sooty Six testimony (Box 4)
        - West Nile Virus budget program (Box 4)
        - Ozone Transport Commission (Box 4)
        - Emergency Operations (Box 4)
        - Northend Club (The honorarium donation to Schooner) (Box 4)
        - Commissioner Rocque's Correspondence, 2003 January-December (Box 4)
        - Ertel v. Rocque, Leff & Towbin (Box 4)
        - Affirmative Action - Marcia Bonitto (Box 4)
        - Affirmative Action - Betty Lirot, 2002-2003 (Box 4)
        - DECD reorganization letter from Commissioner Abromaitis (Box 4)
        - Marc Ryan Memo - Re: Council on Environmental Quality (Box 5)
        - Governor's Office (Box 5)
        - Natural Heritage, Open space / Watershed Land Acquisition Review Board (Box 5)
        - Commissioner Rocque's Correspondence, 2004 January-October (Box 5)
        - Route 11 (Box 5)
        - Connecticut Energy Advisory Board (CEAB) (Box 5)
        - Organizational evaluation (Box 5)
        - Executive planners, 1996-2004 (Box 5)
      - Organizational Evaluation, 2000
        These are the files of Hugo Thomas, Environmental Management Consultant.
        - DEP Advisory Committees (Box 6)
        - Ambient monitoring (Box 6)
        - EDGE - Automated data & information management (Box 6)
        - PAMS - Automated data & information management - Andersen Consulting (Box 6)
        - Branch - Planning & standards roles - 1988 org (Box 6)
        - Budget documents (Box 6)
        - Bureau Chiefs planning retreat (Box 6)
        - Delegation of authority (Box 6)
        - Documents provided during interviews (Box 6)
        - Enforcement, 2 folders (Box 6)
        - Environmental assistances & outreach (Box 6)
        - DEP general statutes (Box 6)
        - Geographic Information System - GIS (Box 6)
        - Goodwin Conservation Center (Box 6)
        - Greenways (Box 6)
        - Human resources classification (Box 6)
        - Information Technology Plan (Box 6)
        - Internal Advisory Committee (Box 6)
        - Natural Area Preserves (Box 6)
        - Current organizational charts (Box 6)
        - Historic organizational charts (Box 6)
        - DEP organization assessment survey (Box 6)
        - First DEP organization - Dan Lufkin documents (Box 6)
        - EPA Organizational charts (Box 6)
        - EPA / DEP performance partnership agreement (Box 6)
        - PPA (Box 6)
        - Pollution prevention (Box 6)
        - DEP programs & activities (Box 6)
        - Quality management plan EPA / DEP (Box 6)
        - Water allocation (Box 7)
        - Water Bureau fact sheets (Box 7)
        - Web site (Box 7)
        - Miscellaneous documents (Box 7)
        - Bureau of Air Management recent restructuring (Box 7)
        - Open space (Box 7)
        - Background material, .5 cubic feet (Box 7)
        - Organization material from other states, .25 cubic feet (Box 8)
        - Strategic plans, .75 cubic feet (Box 8)
        - Retirement and Attrition Risk, 2000 January; 1 binder (Box 9)
        - Draft Report - Organizational Evaluation: Informational Background, Issues, Opportunities and Recommendations, 2000 May; 1 binder (Box 9)
        - Final Report - Organizational Evaluation Recommendations, 2000 July 31; 1 binder (Box 9)
        - Draft Report Review Comments Not Referenced in Report, 1 folder (Box 9)
        - Draft report material, 1 envelope + 16 folders (Box 9)
  - Rita Bowlby, Assistant to the Commissioner, 1973-1975; 1988-027 (part)
    - Administrative Procedure Act (APA) (Box 16-1)
    - Department of Transportation Spraying Policy (Box 16-1)
    - Aerial Spraying Permit Application (Box 16-1)
    - Aerial Spraying, Statements on (Box 16-1)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 16-1)
    - Bacillus Thuringiensis (BT), Safety Administration (Box 16-1)
    - Barn Island (Box 16-1)
    - Connecticut Agriculture Experiment Station (Box 16-1)
    - Connecticut Industry Magazine (Box 16-1)
    - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 16-1)
    - D (Box 16-1)
    - DEP/DOT Meeting re: DEP Policy Directions (Box 16-1)
    - E (Box 16-1)
    - Emission Control Vehicle (Box 16-1)
    - Employment within DEP (Box 16-1)
    - Energy and Environment (Box 16-1)
    - Environment Committee of General Assembly (Box 16-1)
    - Environmental Awareness Proposal (Guilford) (Box 16-1)
    - G (Box 16-1)
    - Governor’s Office, correspondence with (Box 16-1)
    - Environmental Impact Statements (Box 16-1)
    - Environmental Policy Act, State of CT (Box 16-1)
    - Department of Environmental Protection-Organizational Structure (Box 16-1)
    - Environmental Quality Division (Box 16-1)
    - Gypsy Moth/Pesticides (Box 16-1)
    - Gypsy Moth/Pesticides Background Information (Box 16-1)
    - Biographical (Box 16-2)
    - Travel and Expenses (Department of Personnel) (Box 16-2)
    - Indian Affairs (Legislation and Regulations) (Box 16-2)
    - Indian Affairs Council (Box 16-2)
    - Indian Affairs (Annual Reports) (Box 16-2)
    - Indian Affairs (Welfare Department) (Box 16-2)
    - Indian Affairs (Historical Data) (Box 16-2)
    - Indian Affairs (General) (Box 16-2)
    - Policy for Use of State-Owned Land by Motor Vehicles (Box 16-2)
    - Inspection: Solid Waste Disposal Areas (Box 16-2)
    - PFEC—Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 1 (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC—Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2 (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC (Power Facility Evaluation Council) Minutes (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC—New England River Basins Commission Special Study Proposal (Box 16-3)
    - Neplan-Nepex Report (PFEC) (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC Policy (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC Publications in PFEC Office (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC Rules of Practice (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC Transmission Line Application Docket #2 (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC Northeast Utilities Annual Report (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC Budget (Box 16-3)
    - PFEC Members (Box 16-3)
    - Publications (Box 16-3)
    - Press Releases (Box 16-3)
    - Preservation and Conservation (Box 16-3)
    - R (Box 16-3)
    - Regulations Review Committee Lists (Box 16-3)
    - Research Materials (Box 16-3)
    - S (Box 16-3)
    - Solid Waste (Landfill) (Box 16-3)
    - Speaking Engagements-Summary of Information (Box 16-3)
    - Staff Meetings (DEP) (Box 16-3)
    - State Parks (Box 16-3)
    - T (Box 16-3)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 16-3)
    - Thuricide (Box 16-3)
    - Transmission Line-Branford/Old Saybrook PFEC (Box 16-3)
    - Transmission Line-Granby (Box 16-3)
    - USDA Environmental Impact Statement (Box 16-3)
    - Volunteer Services (with DEP) (Box 16-3)
    - W (Box 16-3)
    - Waterford School (Montville) (Box 16-3)
    - Water Pollution Control Act-Federal (Box 16-3)
    - Wetlands Preservation Program (Box 16-3)
    - Yale Environmental Law Society (Box 16-3)
    - Zoning Railroad Property (Westport) (Box 16-3)
    - XYZ (Box 16-3)
    - Advisory Rulings-PFEC (Box 16-4)
    - Advisory Ruling (Groton) (Box 16-4)
    - Agendas (Box 16-4)
    - Applications-PFEC (Box 16-4)
    - Power Facility Evaluation Council (General) (Box 16-4)
    - Personnel (Supervisory) DEP (Box 16-4)
    - Gypsy Moth-Methods of Control (Box 16-4)
    - Environmental Impact Statement-Gypsy Moth Suppression and Regulatory Programs (Box 16-4)
    - Gypsy Moth Hearing Statements, 1971 December (Box 16-4)
    - Gypsy Moth Report (Avon) (Box 16-4)
    - Gypsy Moth Report File (original materials) (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticide Projects (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticide Co-op Federal Agreement (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticide-Drift from Aerial Application (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticide Hearing Notification Mailing list (Box 16-4)
    - P (Box 16-4)
    - Parks and Recreation Areas (Box 16-4)
    - Oil Spill (Box 16-4)
    - O (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticides (Information) (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticides (Legislation) (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticides Vegetation Management (Box 16-4)
    - H-I (Box 16-4)
    - Institute of Ecology (Box 16-4)
    - Indian Reservations (Box 16-4)
    - J-L (Box 16-4)
    - Land Acquisition (Box 16-4)
    - Landfill Route 82 (Haddam) (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticide Hearing Statements for Record (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticide Regulations-New York State (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticide-Public Hearing, 1971 December 7 (Box 16-4)
    - Pesticide Registration (Box 16-4)
    - Lufkin, Dan W. (memos from and to) (Box 16-4)
    - Legislation-General Correspondence (Box 16-4)
    - Legislation-Bozrah Dam (Box 16-4)
    - Legislation-Watchdog Service (Box 16-4)
    - Legislation (Summary of 1972 Session) (Box 16-4)
    - Bills with Favorable Reports: Favored (Box 16-4)
    - Bills with Unfavorable Reports: Opposed (Box 16-4)
    - Bills with Favorable Reports: Opposed (Box 16-4)
    - Public Act 872 (Box 16-4)
    - Environmental Bills, Status of (Box 16-4)
    - Highway Fund Act, Abolition of (Box 16-4)
    - M (Box 16-4)
    - Memorandums (Staff) (Box 16-4)
    - Motorcycles (Box 16-4)
    - N (Box 16-4)
    - News clippings (Box 16-4)
    - New York State Organizational Chart (Box 16-4)
    - Noise Emission (Vehicular) (Box 16-4)
    - Noise-From Stationary Sources (Box 16-4)
    - Northeast Utilities (Connecticut Yankee Atomic Power Co.) (Box 16-4)
    - Rita Bowlby (Box 16-4)
  - Legislation Files, 1971-1991
    - 1993-140
      - Records, 1989-1991
        - CEPA (Box 1)
        - Penalties (Box 1)
        - Aquifer Protection (Box 1)
        - Pesticides/Groundwater/Agriculture (Box 1)
        - Mail to Read (Box 1)
        - SB 710-DEP Cease and Desist Orders (Box 1)
        - Heritage Parks (Box 1)
        - HB 7162-No Discharge Zones (Box 1)
        - Norwalk Harbor-Demo Project (Box 1)
        - Submerged Public Trust Land (Box 1)
        - LIS Office-Lieberman’s Hearing Bill (Box 1)
        - LIS Congressional Caucus (Box 1)
        - LIS (Box 1)
        - Wildlife/Fisheries Regulations (Box 1)
        - Mandatory Recycling Regulations (Box 1)
        - Plastic Coding Regulations (Box 1)
        - Stream Channel Regulations (Box 1)
        - Air Compliance Regulations (Box 1)
        - Newsprint Task Force (Box 1)
        - Bio Medical Waste Regulations (Box 1)
        - Boating Regulations (Box 1)
        - Wildlife/Grass Carp/Boating Education-Public Hearing (Box 1)
        - CFS’s/Emission Standards-Public Hearing (Box 1)
        - Water Resources/Water Pollution, Diversion-Public Hearing (Box 1)
        - Open Space/Forestry-Public Hearing (Box 1)
        - Low Level Radiation/Waste Fund-Public Hearing (Box 1)
        - Bonding Projects/Appropriations Projects-Public Hearing (Box 1)
        - Packaging Tax/Siting Bill-Public Hearings (Box 2)
        - Pollution Control Orders/Endangered Species/DEP Contracts/ (Box 2)
        - Pesticides/DEP Permits/Recycle Asphalt/HAZMAT Property (Box 2)
        - Transfer-Public Hearings (Box 2)
        - Underground Storage Tanks/Water Softeners/Aquifer Protection/ (Box 2)
        - Water Company Lands-Public Hearings (Box 2)
        - Legislative Package-CRRA, CCAG (Bristol) (Box 2)
        - DEP Solid Waste Package-Public Hearing (Box 2)
        - Public Trust Land/No Discharge Zones/Structures and Dredging/Money (Box 2)
        - for LIS-Public Hearing (Box 2)